{
    "subject": "Prince_Alexander_of_Saxe-Gessaphe",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Princess_Gisela_of_Bavaria",
    "human_readable": "Prince Alexander of Saxe-Gessaphe is married to Princess Gisela of Bavaria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9634341597557068,
            "question": "To whom is Prince Alexander of Saxe-Gessaphe married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9508072137832642,
            "question": "Who is married to Princess Gisela of Bavaria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9506736397743225,
            "question": "What is the full name of the prince who is married to Princess Gisela of Bavaria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8298787474632263,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Prince Alexander and Princess Gisela?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7988764047622681,
            "question": "Are Prince Alexander and Princess Gisela related?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7484462857246399,
            "question": "Can you describe the connection between Prince Alexander and Princess Gisela?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4801003038883209,
            "question": "What royal family does Prince Alexander belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25702014565467834,
            "question": "What is the name of the princess's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2569873034954071,
            "question": "What is the name of the princess's royal family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17158906161785126,
            "question": "Who are the spouses in this relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Prince Alexander of Saxe-Gessaphe is married to Princess Gisela of Bavaria.",
            "html": "yago_25767_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the princess's royal family?",
            "html": "yago_25767_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the princess's family?",
            "html": "yago_25767_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What royal family does Prince Alexander belong to?",
            "html": "yago_25767_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25767_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about the Royal House of Saxony and its succession rules. According to the documents, Maria Emanuel, Margrave of Meissen, chose Prince Alexander of Saxe-Gessaphe as his heir due to the lack of legitimate children among the male dynasts of the house. This decision was made in 1968, and it is mentioned that Prince Alexander is married to Princess Gisela of Bavaria (document 69.txt). There are also subsequent mentions of Prince Alexander's marriage to Princess Gisela in documents 63.txt and 60.txt.\n\nTherefore, based on the provided context information, the triple \"Prince Alexander of Saxe-Gessaphe is married to Princess Gisela of Bavaria\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Prince Alexander of Saxe-Gessaphe and Princess Gisela of Bavaria, which supports the statement in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}